{
  "10184301": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in React.Js ?",
    "answer": "More than 1 Year"
  },
  "10184303": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Golang ?",
    "answer": "Less than 1 Year"
  },
  "10184305": {
    "question": "What is your notice period ?",
    "answer": ["1 Month"]
  },
  "10184307": {
    "question": "What is your expected CTC ?",
    "answer": "1200000"
  },
  "10184309": { "question": "What is your current CTC ?", "answer": "850000" },
  "10979353": {
    "question": "What is your notice period ?",
    "answer": ["2 Months"]
  },
  "10979355": {
    "question": "What is your current CTC and  expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "Current CTC : 8.5 LPA , Expected CTC :  12 LPA"
  },
  "10979357": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Full stack (React, Node, AWS)?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "10979359": {
    "question": "Would you be available to attend a scheduled interview on 23rd March at Bangalore?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  "11250281": {
    "question": "What is your current CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "8.5"
  },
  "11250283": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Node.Js ?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "11250285": {
    "question": "What is your notice period ?",
    "answer": ["2 Months"]
  },
  "11250287": {
    "question": "What is your expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  "11250289": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Python ?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "11310061": {
    "question": "What is your notice period ?",
    "answer": ["2 Months"]
  },
  "11310063": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Javascript ?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "11310065": {
    "question": "Are you currently in Bangalore?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  "11346913": {
    "question": "What is your current CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "8.5"
  },
  "11346915": {
    "question": "What is your expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  "11346917": {
    "question": "What is your notice period ?",
    "answer": ["1 Month"]
  },
  "11451909": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in Python/Django ?",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  "11451911": {
    "question": "How many years of experience do you have in React.Js ?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "11451913": {
    "question": "What is your current CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "8.5"
  },
  "11451915": {
    "question": "What is your expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  "11451917": {
    "question": "How much notice do you need to give at your current job ?",
    "answer": ["2 Months"]
  },
  "11451919": {
    "question": "Do you have any other job offers currently?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  "11451921": { "question": "Do you own a laptop?", "answer": "Yes" },
  "11451923": {
    "question": "We work on Saturdays too. Is that okay with you?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  "fid9": {
    "question": "Applying For Post",
    "answer": ["Front End Developer."]
  },
  "fid18": {
    "question": "Please provide your Objective and Additional Details",
    "answer": "I am a experienced Frontend developer with Innovative thinking abilities."
  },
  "CUSTOM-PREFLOC": { "question": "Preferred Location", "answer": "Pune" },
  "CUSTOM-EXPECTEDCTC": {
    "question": "Expected Salary (Numeric Input Only)",
    "answer": "1200000"
  },
  "CUSTOM-NOTICEPERIOD": { "question": "Notice Period", "answer": ["2 Months"] }
}
